What?
لما؟
Su Jinxia from the other courtyard is fake.
Su Jinxia من الفناء الآخر مزيفة.
Yes,
نعم،
When I sneaked into the courtyard,
عندما تسللت إلى الفناء ،
I found that the real Su Jinxia wasn't there,
وجدت أن Su Jinxia الحقيقي لم يكن موجودًا ،
Only one substitute is there
هناك بديل واحد فقط
Su Jinxia is not in the courtyard,
Su Jinxia ليست في الفناء ،
Is it possible that Qin Molin doesn't know
هل من الممكن أن تشين مولين لا يعرف
what's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Continue to investigate Su Jinxia's whereabouts,
استمر في التحقيق في مكان وجود Su Jinxia ،
and once you find him,
وبمجرد أن تجده ،
No need to report.
لا حاجة للإبلاغ.
Kill him immediately.
اقتله على الفور.
Yes, Your Highness.
نعم سموكم.
Why are you still standing there?
لماذا لا تزال واقفا هناك؟
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
in a few days,
في أيام قليلة،
Qin Molin will go hunting in the paddock,
سيذهب تشين مولين للصيد في الحقل ،
which is a good chance to get rid of him.
وهي فرصة جيدة للتخلص منه.
Qin Molin, I have my own plans,
تشين مولين ، لدي خططي الخاصة ،
Yes.
نعم.
What?
لما؟
The Holy Lord still refuses to kill Qin Molin.
لا يزال الرب المقدس يرفض قتل تشين مولين.
The Holy Lord is stubborn,
الرب قدوس عنيد ،
Please listen to Lord Sha's decision.
يرجى الاستماع إلى قرار اللورد شا.
Master can't see clearly sometimes,
السيد لا يرى بوضوح في بعض الأحيان ،
so he needs us as his subordinates,
لذلك فهو بحاجة إلينا كمرؤوسين له ،
Choose a path forward for her.
اختر طريقًا للأمام لها.
Your Excellency, you mean.
معالي الوزير تقصد.
Kill,
قتل،
Yes.
نعم.
My Lady,
سيدتي،
you're not really going to make a bet
لن تقوم بالمراهنة حقًا
with Shopkeeper Chen.
مع تشن صاحب متجر.
If you lose,
لو خسرت،
don't you want to bark like a dog?
ألا تريد أن تنبح كالكلب؟
How can this work?
كيف يمكن أن يعمل هذا؟
My Lady,
سيدتي،
you are the body of a daughter,
انت جسد بنت
What's the point of barking like a dog?
ما الهدف من نباح الكلب؟
I won't lose a piece of meat.
لن أفقد قطعة من اللحم.
But.
لكن.
A big girl can bend and stretch.
يمكن للفتاة الكبيرة أن تنحني وتمتد.
Besides,
بجانب،
Why do you think I'm going to lose?
لماذا تعتقد أنني سأخسر؟
You look down on me.
أنت تنظر إلي باستخفاف.
No.
لا.
I bet with Chen Jie,
أراهن مع تشين جي ،
just to promote a large-size women's clothing store.
فقط للترويج لمتجر ملابس نسائي كبير الحجم.
Ah,
آه،
Think about it,
فكر في الأمر،
Chen Jie's ready-to-wear shop
محل تشين جي للملابس الجاهزة
is one of the best in our capital,
هي واحدة من الأفضل في عاصمتنا ،
I bet with him,
أراهن معه ،
if I win,
إن فزت،
Then you'll surely become famous in the capital city.
عندها ستصبح بالتأكيد مشهورًا في العاصمة.
If you lose,
لو خسرت،
it can also have a certain publicity effect.
يمكن أن يكون لها أيضًا تأثير دعاية معين.
We won't lose money this time.
لن نخسر المال هذه المرة.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
What about you,
ماذا عنك،
Pearl?
لؤلؤة؟
Just keep an eye on the store.
فقط راقب المتجر.
You're just in time.
أنت في الوقت المناسب.
Come with me to the street.
تعال معي إلى الشارع.
Do you have a suitable model?
هل لديك موديل مناسب؟
Okay.
تمام.
Boss
رئيس
You're a fast learner.
أنت سريع التعلم.
Look,
ينظر،
look at her fat face,
انظر إلى وجهها السمين ،
There's a fat girl here,
هناك فتاة سمينة هنا ،
whose butt is almost as big as mine.
الذي بعقب كبير مثل لي.
What nonsense are you talking about?
ما هذا الهراء الذي تتحدث عنه؟
It's three.
إنها ثلاثة.
She's fatter than a pig,
انها سمنة من الخنزير ،
If I were so fat,
إذا كنت سمينًا جدًا ،
I would have killed myself,
كنت سأقتل نفسي ،
Come on,
تعال،
let's go back and eat some pig food.
دعنا نعود ونأكل بعض طعام الخنازير.
Get out of the way!
ابتعد عن الطريق!
Where else can you go?
أين يمكنك الذهاب؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Ouch,
أوتش ،
Who hit me?
من ضربني؟
Hum,
همم،
It's your aunt, me,
انها عمتك انا
fatso,
سمين ،
You don't want to live anymore, do you?
أنت لا تريد أن تعيش بعد الآن ، أليس كذلك؟
I'll teach you a lesson.
سألقنك درس.
Wu Yue,
وو يو ،
Humph.
همف.
Let's go!
لنذهب!
That's the way it is.
هكذا هي.
I don't know what's wrong
أنا لا أعرف ما الخطأ
with models, do I?
مع النماذج ، أليس كذلك؟
But,
لكن،
if I can help Miss Su,
إذا كان بإمكاني مساعدة الآنسة سو ،
I'm willing to give it a try.
أنا على استعداد لتجربته.
That's great.
هذا عظيم.
Without further ado,
دون مزيد من اللغط،
Pearl,
لؤلؤة،
You help Juan measure himself.
أنت تساعد خوان في قياس نفسه.
What about me?
ماذا عني؟
Now I'm going to find some materials
الآن سأجد بعض المواد
in the woods. I'll go with you.
في الغابة.  سأذهب معك.
I'd better not.
من الأفضل أن لا.
You're so weak.
أنت ضعيف جدا.
If you faint,
إذا أغمي عليك
I have to carry you back.
لا بد لي من إعادتك.
I'll be right back.
سأعود حالا.
I'm leaving.
سأرحل.
Miss, come back early.
آنسة ، عد مبكرا.
I have a little donkey,
لدي حمار صغير
and she never rides it.
وهي لم تركبها أبدًا.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
And he got hurt.
وقد أصيب.
Is it another plot of rebellion?
هل هي مؤامرة تمرد أخرى؟
It's such a dangerous matter,
إنها مسألة خطيرة ،
I'd better stay out of it.
من الأفضل أن أبقى خارجها.